Guide to the Gene Federico Papers, 1918-2003 and undated, bulk 1951-1991 RL.00383
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Photographs and Negatives Series, circa 1939-2001 and undated, bulk 1951-1996
  - Photographs (Box 13)
    - Graphic design
      - H design (typographic design for Hennessy), undated (Box 13)
      - Men on cards, undated (Box 13)
      - Metal AD shape, undated (Box 13)
      - Pencil in a knot (IBM advertisement component), undated (Box 13)
      - Unidentified (black and white glass), undated (Box 13)
    - Of Federico (Business)
      - Art Directors Club
        - ADC exhibition poster, 1959 (Box 13)
        - ADC promotion: For Ads Only: Photography to Relax By, 1960 (Box 13)
      - Awards, 1974, 1984 (Box 13)
      - Biographical promotion (photograph and blurb), circa 1980s (Box 13)
      - Conferences/Exhibits, 1951, 1966, 1985 and undated (Box 13)
      - Contact sheets
        - 1960 and 1964 (Box 13)
        - Undated, 2 folders (Box 13)
      - Mounted photos, undated (Box 13)
      - Portraits, 1979, 1988, 1997 and undated (Box 13)
        [One portrait of Federico accompanied by correspondence from photographer Jim Salzano.]
      - Various
        - Black and white, undated (Box 13)
        - Photocopied originals, circa 1939-1990 and undated (Box 13)
    - Personal/Family
      - Tom Benrimo, undated (Box 13)
      - Dinners/Receptions
        - Black and white, undated (Box 13)
        - Color, 1967-1986 and undated (Box 13)
      - Federico portraits
        - Black and white, circa 1940, 1999 and undated (Box 13)
        - Color, 1970s-1982 (Box 13)
      - Tennis/Sporting, 1979, 1996 and undated (Box 13)
      - Various (black and white), 1941-1979 (Box 13)
      - World War II (photocopied originals), circa 1940s (Box 13)
  - Negatives, 1960-1991 and undated (Box 14)
    - Advertisements
      - Disney Hats, undated (Box 14)
      - Doubleday Dictionary, undated (Box 14)
      - Harvey's Bristol Cream, 1963 (Box 14)
      - IBM, undated (Box 14)
      - Jana handbags, undated (Box 14)
      - L'Aiglon Apparel, undated (Box 14)
      - Lambretta scooter ( Innocenti Corporation), 1954 (Box 14)
      - Movado
        - Movado/ Christian Dior, undated (Box 14)
        - Movado Collection: Museum Watch, undated (Box 14)
      - Napier/ Elizabeth Arden, 1983, 1987 and undated (Box 14)
      - The New Yorker, undated (Box 14)
      - RCA Victor Television, undated (Box 14)
      - Supima cotton, undated (Box 14)
      - Woman's Day: Bicycle advertisement, undated (Box 14)
    - Graphic design
      - Abraham Lincoln High School: Silver Anniversary program (featuring Gabriel R. Mason), 1955 (Box 14)
      - Announcements/Cards
        - DDS Advertising (Douglas D. Simon), undated (Box 14)
        - Family card designs, 1976, 1984-1988 and undated (Box 14)
        - Four Veterans exhibit/William Bell, undated (Box 14)
        - Moving announcements
          - Moved/Disraeli advertisement, undated (Box 14)
          - We Moved, undated (Box 14)
        - Toni Ficalora Studio, 1958 (Box 14)
          [Also contains negatives for one cover design (Interiors: Industrial Design) and an advertisement for the Cotton Producers Institute. These negatives are attached to Toni Ficalora negatives.]
        - Various, 1976 and undated (Box 14)
      - Covers
        - The Other Side, 1991 (Box 14)
        - The Wolf That Fed Us (Robert Lowry) book cover, undated (Box 14)
      - Posters
        - ADC exhibition poster, 1960 (Box 14)
        - American Institute of Graphic Arts: Call poster, 1955 (Box 14)
        - Cryptographics, undated (Box 14)
        - Red paint/hand, undated (Box 14)
        - 1984, 1984 (Box 14)
      - Stationery: M. Sokolsky, undated (Box 14)
      - Other designs (additional designs)
        - The Girl Who Hated Men article, undated (Box 14)
        - Hand and bent screw, undated (Box 14)
        - Love of Apples selection, undated (Box 14)
        - Metal AD shape, undated (Box 14)
        - Page 10 (from the 24-Page Book), 1987 (Box 14)
        - Pencil in a knot/silver cone (2 images), undated (Box 14)
        - Sphere and safety pin, undated (Box 14)
        - Technique Silver-Tone (features Federico?), undated (Box 14)
        - 25 design (anniversary?), undated (Box 14)
        - 70 Year Odyssey (personal biography), circa late 1990s (Box 14)
    - Of Federico (Business)
      - Contact sheets, 1972 (Box 14)
        [Contains 35 negative strips total, primarily portraits of Federico and associates for LGFE agency promotion.]
      - Federico portrait (black and white), undated (Box 14)
      - Federico/Three hands design, undated (Box 14)
- Videocassettes Series, 1989-1999 and undated
  Contains video recordings of television commercials for clients including the American Cancer Society, Elizabeth Arden, and Bufferin. Also includes a tribute video to Federico prepared by the Art Directors Club following his death in 1999, and an unedited video documenting a day in the life of Gene Federico. Arranged into three catgories - Original Materials, Preservation Masters, and Use Copies - and alphabetically therein. Total running time (TRT), if known, shown in parentheses.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  [Originals closed to patron use. Some use copies available in the collection. Otherwise, Technical Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed. Please contact Research Services staff before coming to use this series.]
  - Original Materials - VHS Videocassettes (CLOSED) (Box 15)
    - OR1. Gene Federico Tribute Video - ADC, 1998 July. (TRT 7:06) (Box 15)
    - OR2. Gene Federico Tribute Video (edited version), 1999 Oct. 21 (Box 15)
    - OR3. GF - AT/ITC, undated (Box 15)
    - OR4. GF TVC, undated. (TRT 2:30) (Box 15)
      [Includes television commercials for the American Cancer Society: Cowboys, Gambling; Elizabeth Arden: Visible Difference.]
    - OR5. GF TVCs, undated (Box 15)
      [Includes television commercials for Elizabeth Arden: Blue Grass cologne, and Bufferin cold tablets.]
    - OR6. GF Voice-Over, 1990 Mar. 12 (Box 15)
      [Contains television commercials for America's Insurance Companies, including segments entitled Professor, Immigrant, and Small Town. Federico provided the voiceover for the Professor segment on Professor Frank Barnes.]
    - OR7. PRINT's Best International Commercials: Selected from the Cannes Festival, 1989 (Box 15)
  - Master Copies MC1-MC3 (Not for reference use)
    - MC1 (Box 15)
    - MC2 (Box 15)
    - MC3 (Box 15)
  - Use Copies UC1-UC4 (Box 14)
    - UC1
      - Gene Federico Tribute Video (edited version), 1999 Oct. 21 (Box 14)
    - UC2
      - GF - AT/ITC, undated (Box 14)
    - UC3
      - GF TVC, undated (Box 14)
      - GF TVCs, undated (Box 14)
      - GF Voice-Over, 1990 Mar. 12 (Box 14)
    - UC4
      - PRINT'S Best International Commercials: Selected from the Cannes Festival, 1989 (Box 14)
- Oversize Materials
  Primarily includes materials from the Graphic Design Series and Advertising Campaigns Series. Also contains materials from the Professional Files Series and Personal Files Series, and folders of large format materials from the Photographs and Negatives Series. Clients represented include Christian Dior, Elizabeth Arden, Goldman Sachs, IBM, Jo Collins, L'Aiglon Apparel, Lady Pepperell, and Max Factor. Materials of particular interest include two posters Federico designed for the U.S. Army: Conceal your shadow...as well as yourself(1942) and a peace poster(1944). Arranged within original series, therein alphabetically by subject/client.
  - Professional Files Series, circa 1950s-1999 and undated (Box OV1)
    - Art Directors Club: An Evening With One of the Best: Gene Federico, undated (Box OV1)
    - Awards and exhibits: Honorary Doctorate, Parson's School of Design (photocopy), 1990 May 12 (Box OV1)
    - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, undated (Box OV1)
    - Federico portraits (caricature, photomechanical print), 1979 and 1987 (Box OV1)
    - Industry Publications
      - High Quality magazine: Cryptographics and other articles, 1986, 1989, and 1994 (Box OV1)
      - Pratt Reports, 1979 Summer (Box OV1)
    - Press clippings
      - Daily News Magazine: The Camera '90: Ultimate Yearbook, NYC's Most Famous High School Grads, 1990 June 17 (Box OV1)
      - Esquire magazine: The 100 Best People in the World, 1965 Aug. (Box OV1)
      - The New York Times Magazine: Report on Men's Wear: An Art Director's Eye for Clothes, 1976 Sept. 19 (Box OV1)
      - Wall Street Journal: Creative Leaders insert, 1983 and 1987 (Box OV1)
      - Various (On Federico), 1964-1972, 1989 and undated (Box OV1)
      - Various (miscellaneous), 1959, 1971, 1984 and undated (Box OV1)
    - Writings
      - Kyla Gill, Gene Federico: A Profile of the World Renowned Advertising Designer, 1999 (Box OV1)
      - Paul Rand article: Gene and Helen Federico, Graphis, circa 1950s (Box OV1)
  - Personal Files Series, 1918-1991 and undated (Box OV1)
    - The New York Times (front page), 1918 Feb. 6 (Box OV1)
    - Original artwork
      - Monotint etching, undated (Box OV1)
      - San Valentio, Abruzzi drawing (Gene and Helen Federico), 1971 (Box OV1)
      - Sketches, 1977 and undated (Box OV1)
      - Various (pigeon collage, siamese twins, musicians), 1940 and undated (Box OV1)
    - Pratt Grad newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box OV1)
    - World War II materials
      - Peace Poster, 1944 (Box OV1)
      - Sketchbooks - Brown cover (insert), undated (Box OV1)
  - Photographs and Negatives Series, 1959-1980s and undated (Box OV1)
    - Photographs
      - Advertisements
        - Albert Einstein (for Vogue), undated (Box OV1)
        - Harvey's sherry, undated (Box OV1)
        - Parfums de Corday: Toujours Moi perfume, undated (Box OV1)
        - Seagram's Gin, undated (Box OV1)
        - Tanner apparel: It's a Love, It's Tanner campaign, undated (Box OV1)
        - Various (miscellaneous babies), undated (Box OV1)
      - Graphic design
        - H design (typographic design), undated (Box OV1)
        - Men on cards, undated (Box OV1)
      - Of Federico (Business)
        - Art Directors Club
          - ADC exhibition poster, 1959 (Box OV1)
          - ADC promotion: For Ads Only: Photography to Relax By, 1960 (Box OV1)
            [Photograph features Gene Federico reclining.]
        - Biographical promotion (photo and blurb), circa 1980s (Box OV1)
        - Portraits, undated (Box OV1)
        - Various, undated (Box OV1)
  - Professional Files Series, 1971-1992 and undated (Box OV2)
    - Awards and exhibits
      - Conference brochures - Various, 1971, 1979 and 1987 (Box OV2)
      - Pioneer-Moss contest, 1968 and undated (Box OV2)
    - Federico caricature: signed by artist Al Hirschfeld, undated (Box OV2)
      [Print with caricature of Federico, signed by New York Times caricature artist Al Hirschfeld.]
    - Press clippings
      - Il Manifesto: Napoli poster design article, 1986 Oct. 18 (Box OV2)
      - New York Times Magazine: Report on Men's Wear, 1976 Sept. 19 (Box OV2)
      - Pound Ridge Review: Gene and Helen Federico, Life of Shared Achievements, 1992 Oct. 15 (Box OV2)
      - Wall Street Journal, Creative Leaders insert: Seen By Gene, 1981 (Box OV2)
    - Writings
      - Steven Heller, Gene Federico: The Art Director's Art Director, undated (Box OV2)
  - Personal Files Series, 1942 and 1955 (Box OV2)
    - Abraham Lincoln High School
      - Silver anniversary luncheon - program design, 1955 (Box OV2)
    - World War II materials
      - Poster: Conceal your shadow... as well as yourself, 1942 (Box OV2)
  - Graphic Design Series, 1938-1992 and undated (Box OV2)
    - Additional designs
      - Art and Illustration (for Chris Collins?), hand/cube in red paint, undated (Box OV2)
      - Cryptographics, undated (Box OV2)
      - My Message is a Simple One design, undated (Box OV2)
      - Page 10 (from the 24-Page Book), 1987 (Box OV2)
    - Announcements/Cards
      - American Institute of Graphic Design: Call for Entries: 14th Annual Exhibition, 1955 (Box OV2)
      - Art Director's Club
        - Call for Arms contest and exhibit (cosponsored with Pioneer-Moss), undated (Box OV2)
        - 39th Annual Exhibition, 1960 and undated (Box OV2)
      - Holiday cards
        - Federico family, 1970, 1980, 1990 and undated (Box OV2)
    - Calendars, 1984-1997 and undated
      - DC & A, undated (Box OV2)
      - PM Typography, 1984/1985 (Box OV2)
      - SPER (Italian), 1988 (Box OV2)
    - Client catalogs/brochures
      - Abbott Kimball Co. Inc.: Publicity brochure, 1938 (Box OV2)
      - Jo Collins: every season is a Jo Collins season brochure, undated (Box OV2)
      - Museum of Art, Science and Industry (Fairfield, Connecticut): promotional brochure, 1959 (Box OV2)
      - UCLA Extension, 1990 Fall (Box OV2)
    - Concepts and sketches - Various, undated (Box OV3)
    - Cover designs
      - Book covers
        - Doubleday
          - Fiction titles, undated (Box OV3)
          - Non-fiction titles, undated (Box OV3)
        - Various, undated (Box OV3)
      - Magazines/Journals
        - Liberty magazine concepts, 1948 and undated (Box OV3)
      - Record covers
        - Lukas Foss, A Parable of Death (Columbia Records), undated (Box OV3)
    - Illustrations
      - The Girl Who Hated Men, John Reese story, undated (Box OV3)
      - One Of Us Must Die, Edmund Gilligan essay, 1962 Sept. 8 (Box OV3)
    - Letterhead/Logo
      - Bishop Color Inc., undated (Box OV3)
      - Forma Art Associates, Ltd. (Films), undated (Box OV3)
    - Posters
      - Hiram Halle Memorial Library: 40th Anniversary, 1992 (Box OV3)
      - New York City's Hudson Celebration, 1959 (Box OV3)
      - Observatoire International Des Prisons, 1992 (Box OV3)
      - PM Typography, 1984 (Box OV3)
      - Reflections: Pound Ridge Garden Club, undated (Box OV3)
      - Tileston & Hollingsworth Company, undated (Box OV3)
    - Typographic materials
      - PM Typography poster, undated (Box OV3)
      - Typeface samples - Various, undated (Box OV3)
    - Other artists/designers
      - ERGO (portfolio of various artists, including Andy Warhol, Bob Sullivan, Jerome Martin ), undated (Box OV3)
      - Larimer, Bob, undated (Box OV3)
      - Lubalin, Herb: Iconochrestomathy, 1966 (Box OV3)
      - Steinberg, Saul and Hedda Sterne, 1951 (Box OV3)
      - Varisco, Tom, undated (Box OV3)
  - Advertising Campaigns Series, 1951-1989 and undated (Box OV4)
    - Clippings and proofs
      - Unmounted advertisements
        - Ban-Lon knitwear (Joseph Bancroft & Sons, Co.), 1964 and undated (Box OV4)
        - Borg Fabrics, circa late 1950s (Box OV4)
        - Caprolan, 1966 (Box OV4)
        - Christian Dior: Wamsutta (linens), undated (Box OV4)
        - Cool-Whip, undated (Box OV4)
        - Corn Silk, 1965 (Box OV4)
        - Duchess (dresses), undated (Box OV4)
        - Einiger Fabrics, 1956 and undated (Box OV4)
        - Elektra Records: The Incredible String Band and The Doors, circa late 1960s (Box OV4)
        - Elizabeth Arden
          - Arden for Men, undated (Box OV4)
          - Cosmetics, 1958 and undated (Box OV4)
        - Firestone Plastics Company, undated (Box OV4)
        - Gay Gibson (women's apparel), undated (Box OV4)
        - Glass Container Manufacturer's Institute, 1963 (Box OV4)
        - Helena Rubinstein (cosmetics), undated (Box OV4)
        - Hollander Furs, 1951 (Box OV4)
        - Hollywood Diet Bread, undated (Box OV4)
        - IBM, 1961-1962 and undated (Box OV4)
        - Jo Collins, 1957 and undated (Box OV4)
        - Lady Pepperell, undated (Box OV4)
        - L'Aiglon Apparel
          - L'Aiglon - General, 1956-1958 and undated (Box OV4)
          - Jeanne d'Arc, 1956 and undated (Box OV4)
        - Lisner, 1957-1959 (Box OV4)
        - Magee (carpets and rugs), undated (Box OV4)
        - Max Factor, undated (Box OV4)
        - Milliken Woolens, 1959 and undated (Box OV4)
        - Mona Lisa: Triomphe girdle, undated (Box OV4)
        - Napier (jewelry), undated (Box OV4)
        - National Cotton Council, 1957-1959 and undated (Box OV4)
        - The New Yorker, 1978-1988 and undated (Box OV4)
          (2 folders)
        - Parfums de Corday (Trapze), 1958 (Box OV4)
        - Pepperell Manufacturing Company, 1964-1965 (Box OV4)
        - Reva (handbags), undated (Box OV4)
        - Schumacher, undated (Box OV4)
        - Supima cotton, circa 1950s (Box OV4)
        - Tecnique Color-Tone (hair dye), 1962-1963 (Box OV4)
        - Vassarette (lingerie), 1981 (Box OV4)
        - Waverly, undated (Box OV5)
        - Wear-Right (gloves), 1953 and undated (Box OV5)
        - Woman's Day, 1953-1955 and undated (Box OV5)
          (2 folders.)
        - Wool Bureau, undated (Box OV5)
        - Wyner (knitwear): Sag-No-Mor wool jersey
          - Dior, circa 1950s (Box OV5)
          - Other designers (Anne Klein, Marion McCoy, Maurice Rentner), 1957 and undated (Box OV5)
      - Mounted advertisements
        - Christian Dior: Wamsutta, undated (Box OV5)
        - Corn Silk (cosmetics), 1965 (Box OV5)
        - Einiger, circa 1950s (Box OV5)
        - Elizabeth Arden, 1971 (Box OV5)
        - Helena Rubinstein (cosmetics), undated (Box OV5)
        - Lady Pepperell, undated (Box OV5)
        - The New Yorker, 1984 and circa 1980 (Box OV5)
        - Stiffel, undated (Box OV5)
        - Tecnique Color Tone (hair dye), circa 1962-1963 (Box OV5)
        - Wear-Right (gloves), undated (Box OV5)
        - Woman's Day, 1953 (Box OV5)
          [Rare page proof of famed She's got to go out to get Woman's Day bicycle advertisment.]
    - Concepts and sketches (Box OV6)
      - American Ballet Theatre, undated (Box OV6)
      - Benton & Bowles, 1960 and undated (Box OV6)
      - Borg, undated (Box OV6)
      - Chandon champagne, 1989 and undated (Box OV6)
      - Container Corporatin of America: Disraeli advertisement, undated (Box OV6)
      - Disney Hats, undated (Box OV6)
      - The Economist, undated (Box OV6)
      - Gay Gibson, undated (Box OV6)
      - Goldman Sachs, undated (Box OV6)
      - Hennessy, undated (Box OV6)
      - IBM, undated (Box OV6)
      - Killington, Vermont, undated (Box OV6)
      - Life Savers, undated (Box OV6)
      - Modecraft (coats): Builders All, Americans All campaign, circa 1950s (Box OV7)
        [Features President Dwight D. Eisenhower, and highlights True Americanism vs. Un-Americanism.]
      - The New Yorker, undated (Box OV7)
      - Pine Bros. (cough drops), undated (Box OV7)
      - Sony, undated (Box OV7)
      - Tecnique Color-Tone (hair dye), circa 1962-1963 (Box OV7)
      - Valentino perfume, undated (Box OV7)
      - Woman's Day, 1953 and undated (Box OV7)
  - Photographs and Negatives Series, 1963-1964, 1997 and undated (Box OV7)
    - Photographs
      - Advertisements
        - Air India, 1964 (Box OV7)
          [Advertisement features Federico.]
        - Chandon champagne: television storyboards, undated (Box OV7)
        - Emeraude, undated (Box OV7)
        - Harvey's Bristol Cream, circa 1963 (Box OV7)
        - Hennessy, undated (Box OV7)
        - IBM (typewriters and dictating machine), undated (Box OV7)
      - Of Federico (Business)
        - Portrait (black and white), 1997 (Box OV7)
  - Professional Files Series, undated (Box OV8 (LARGE OVERSIZE))
    - Writings: By Others
      - Lawrence Miller: Federico career tribute, undated (Box OV8 (LARGE OVERSIZE))
  - Personal Files Series, 1955 and undated (Box OV8)
    - Abraham Lincoln High School: Silver Anniversary Luncheon, 1955 (Box OV8)
    - Original artwork: children's drawing (Gina Federico), undated (Box OV8)
  - Graphic Design Series, 1955-1997 and undated (Box OV8)
    - Announcements/Cards
      - American Institute of Graphic Arts: Call for Entries, 1955-1958 (Box OV8)
      - Family cards: Helen and Gene, 1983 (Box OV8)
    - Calendars
      - Basil Pizza design, 1997 (Box OV8)
      - DC & A: 12 Artists, undated (Box OV8)
    - Concepts and sketches
      - Art Director's Club: entry form, circa 1960 (Box OV8)
      - Components - various, undated (Box OV8)
      - Federico Design, 1989 (Box OV8)
      - 7th Educational Graphic Arts Exposition, 1959 (Box OV8)
    - Cover designs
      - Annual reports: GTE, 1987 (Box OV8)
      - Book covers: 64th Art Directors Annual (ADC Publications), undated (Box OV8)
    - Letterhead/Logo
      - LGFE, undated (Box OV8)
    - Posters
      - Art Director's Club: 39th Annual Exhibition (1960), 1959 (Box OV8)
      - Illustrators XII, 1968 (Box OV8)
      - Various, 1967 and undated (Box OV8)
    - Typographic materials: Typeface samples, undated (Box OV8)
  - Advertising Campaigns Series, 1953-1991 and undated (Box OV9)
    - Clippings and Proofs
      - American Elegance, undated (Box OV9)
      - Borg, undated (Box OV9)
      - Corn Silk, 1965 (Box OV9)
      - Disney Hats, undated (Box OV9)
      - Einiger, undated (Box OV9)
      - Gay Gibson, undated (Box OV9)
      - Lady Pepperell, undated (Box OV9)
      - Magee (carpets and rugs), undated (Box OV9)
      - Max Factor (cosmetics), undated (Box OV9)
      - The New Yorker, 1979, 1988 and undated (Box OV9)
      - Phillips-Jones Corporation: Van Heusen, undated (Box OV9)
      - Reva, undated (Box OV9)
      - Supima, undated (Box OV9)
      - Woman's Day, 1953-1954 and undated (Box OV9)
      - Wool Bureau, undated (Box OV9)
      - Various (Newspaper), 1964-1991 and undated (Box OV9)
    - Concepts and sketches
      - Corn Silk, undated (Box OV9)
      - Emeraude, undated (Box OV9)
      - NE Airlines, undated (Box OV9)
      - The New Yorker, undated (Box OV9)
      - Parfums de Corday, undated (Box OV9)
      - Versace, undated (Box OV9)
      - Woodfield Country Club, undated (Box OV9)
  - Professional Files Series, 1988, 1992 and undated (Oversize-folder OV1-OV2)
    - Awards and exhibits: Various, 1988 and 1992 (Oversize-folder OV1-OV2)
      [Includes materials on Federico's 1987 AIGA Medal and Fashion Institute of Technology event, Gene Federico: Profile of an American Master.]
      [2 items.]
    - Writings (By Others): Steven Heller article/spreads, Gene Federico: An Art Director's Art Director, undated (Oversize-folder OV1-OV2)
  - Graphic Design Series, 1958-1990 and undated (Oversize-folder OV3-OV4)
    - Announcements/Cards: American Institute of Graphic Arts, Graphics in Packaging call for entries, 1958 (Oversize-folder OV3-OV4)
      [1 item.]
    - Announcements/Cards: Holiday Cards (Personal) - Federico family, 1982 (Oversize-folder OV3-OV4)
    - Posters (Oversize-folder OV5-OV6)
      - UCLA Extension, 1990 (Oversize-folder OV5-OV6)
      - Various (Napoli, 1 cent sale), undated (Oversize-folder OV5-OV6)
        [3 items.]
  - Advertising Campaigns Series, 1991 and undated (Oversize-folder OV7-OV10)
    - Clippings and proofs
      - Elizabeth Arden (cosmetics), undated (Oversize-folder OV7-OV10)
        [4 items.]
      - Hart's Seeds, undated (Oversize-folder OV7-OV10)
        [Likely historical advertisement, not by Federico, perhaps used as research.]
    - Concepts and sketches
      - Arthur Andersen, 1991 (Oversize-folder OV7-OV10)
      - Lady Pepperell, undated (Oversize-folder OV7-OV10)